funny-videos.co.uk 2006-12-10

# Privacy Statement for Funny Videos

**Privacy Statement for Funny-Videos.co.uk  
** Funny-videos.co.uk has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: 

**Funny-Videos.co.uk Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example) and IP address only for statistical purposes. 

**Advertisers**  
We use few outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. 

**Personal Information**  
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. The mailinglist provided by Funny-Videos.co.uk uses the "opt in" procedure, meaning that all subscribers have chosen to receive the newsletter on their own will, have personally confirmed their subscription and can at anytime choose to unsubscribe. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites, funny-videos.co.uk is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us by emailing us at [our contact page](http://www.funny-videos.co.uk/email.php).

**Submit Video **| **Privacy Policy **| **[Contact Us](http://www.funny-videos.co.uk/email.php)**

Current Videos: 1197  
Average rating 3.87 (out of 5) from 165152 votes.  
Copyright Funny-Videos.co.uk 2005. All Rights Reserved.
